<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on Guanghua</title>
    <link>/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on Guanghua</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Guanghua Wang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 20:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting pages on Github using Rmarkdown and Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/2017-02-17-set-up-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2017-02-17-set-up-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>My personal website is created by R package blogdown and Hugo1 and is hosted on Github. This page summarise my steps to setup the site.
Creating github repositories Two respositories are needed for the site.
I create blog_hugo to host Hugo’s content)
 I create &amp;lt;my-user-name&amp;gt;.github.io to host the public folder, which contains the static website.
   Installing Blogdown and Hugo Install blogdown. It is under heavy development when I write this blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with the Academic framework for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The Academic framework enables you to easily create a beautifully simple personal or academic website using the Hugo static site generator.
Key features:
 Easily manage your homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Configurable widgets available for Biography, Publications, Projects, News/Blog, Talks, and Contact Need a different section? Just use the Custom widget! Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Social/academic network linking, Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Easy to customize  Installation  Install Hugo and create a new website by typing the following commands in your Terminal or Command Prompt app:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing the homepage with widgets</title>
      <link>/post/widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/widgets/</guid>
      <description>Homepage widgets display as sections on the homepage. They can be enabled/disabled and configured as desired. Academic has the following widgets available to use:
 About/biography Selected publications Recent publications Recent news/blog posts Projects Selected talks Recent talks Contact Custom widget (demonstrated with the teaching example)  The example site that you copied to create your site uses all the different types of widget (except talks), so you can generally just delete the widgets you don&amp;rsquo;t need and customize the parameters of the widgets you wish to keep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing content</title>
      <link>/post/managing-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/managing-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a brief guide to managing content with the Academic framework. Content can include publications, projects, talks, and news/blog articles. After you have read this guide about creating and managing content, you may also be interested to learn about &lt;a href=&#34;/post/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>